<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ItemAssembly name="Logbook Deep Within The Throat" description="very nsfw, husk action" hideinmenus="false">
  <Item name="" identifier="handheldterminal" ID="2016" rect="0,7,17,23" noninteractable="False" nonplayerteaminteractable="False" allowswapping="True" rotation="0" scale="0.25" spritecolor="255,255,255,255" inventoryiconcolor="255,255,255,255" containercolor="255,255,255,255" condition="100" invulnerabletodamage="False" tags="smallitem,logic" displaysidebysidewhenlinked="False" disallowedupgrades="" spritedepth="0.55" hiddeningame="False">
    <Holdable holdpos="0,0" holdangle="30" swingamount="0,0" swingspeed="0" swingwhenholding="False" swingwhenaiming="False" swingwhenusing="False" pickingtime="0" canbepicked="True" allowingameediting="True" msg="ItemMsgPickUpSelect" />
    <Terminal welcomemessage="Gregor had been nursing this erection for far longer than he expected.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;If anything, the reason that he hadn't simply taken care of it himself was because of his situation - trying to jack off wasn't really feasible when his entire body was being sapped of energy to incubate a bunch of extra Husk parasites, even if he was technically infected himself. The constant movements in the depths of his body made it very difficult to focus, let alone maintain a proper hold in his own twitching cock without having to remove his hands and tend to this aching muscles instead.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;At this point, he just wanted to relieve the strain. It was crude, but it was the truth, especially since he had nothing else to entertain himself with. He was infected, so he couldn't drown, wasn't in danger of the ocean's water pressure, and didn't even need to eat or drink: he just had to sit quietly and let his body do its job.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The infested diving suit stomped past him, face-tentacles licking the open water around it like it was trying to 'taste the air'. Its shattered helmet faceplate snapped towards him almost immediately, and the walking corpse stumbled over, vaguely burbling as it approached. Just like last time, the voice of the parasite inside injected itself into Gregor's mind, bouncing around his cells like it was a part of his thoughts. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;You. Aroused?&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Gregor said nothing, shifting his legs slightly - with a hefty groan, due to this uncomfortably compromised state - to cover the raging stiffness in his nude lower half. The idea of being so hard in front of a Husk, of all things, was a little bit sickening.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;You. Scared.&quot; The voice was strained and sore, made from whatever remained of the vocal chords that the original parasite had settled near. &quot;Me?&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;...pretty fucking scared, yeah.&quot; He wasn't sure what he was going to do if it decided to attack him. Die, probably. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Vaguely snarling and gasping at nothing in particular, the Husk pulled itself forward in a warped display of sensuality, pressing its chest up against his legs in a way that defied the limits of a human spinal column. &quot;Incubator. Care. Love.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Even though he didn't need to breathe, Gregor was moving the water's oxygen through his lungs anyway as a force of habit. He felt every bit of 'breath' leave his body at once when the three 'tongues' buried in the Husk's former head slipped out and dangled against his skin, brushing over the goosebumps that he had developed in the cool water. &quot;Hey, what-&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Aroused. Need? Help?&quot; The tendrils lightly coated parts of his body with a thick saliva that didn't wash off in the gentle currents of the wreck's water, something that made his skin tingle on contact, then start to burn a little. &quot;Love.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;There wasn't much that Gregor could do, but he didn't get a chance to excuse himself or deny that there was anything going on. As soon as one of the solid tendrils brushed up against his shaft, he was rock-hard again, involuntarily gasping at the unexpected tension it created in his pelvic muscles. Sucking in air - well, water - through his teeth, he tried to stammer out some kind of apology, but it was clear that one wasn't needed.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A low gurgle made its way out of the creature's mouth as it tilted its head up to look him in the eyes, letting him see the insides of its helmet. There was nothing left of the human that used to inhabit the suit, aside from some chunks and paste-like scraps that had yet to be digested. Meaty flesh pulsated behind the glass, and the three tentacles that had once been part of the host's throat hung in the air, tasting Gregor's fear.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Will. Help.&quot; The tongue touching his cock sprang into action as it slipped downwards and began to wrap itself around his shaft, tightly winding over the sensitive, aching skin with little hesitation. The other two began to follow suit, snaking over to find their preferred spots as well. &quot;Take. Care. Incubator.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Gregor finally grasped what it was trying to say. The Husk wasn't asking him if he needed outside help, it was offering itself as a source of relief. Two feelings flooded his brain: this was extremely fucked up, but it was also very, very hot, and the two weren't cancelling each other out. &quot;You, uh, you don't have to-&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;He didn't get to finish speaking before the other two tendrils hit their mark, one coiling around his cock opposite to the first while the other pushed further downwards, cupping his balls with its soft, meaty skin and giving them a loving squeeze that sent a pulse of adrenaline through his spawn-incubating body. Accidentally groaning at the sudden touches, Gregor noticed that the Husk reacted with confusion, cocking its head to one side and glancing back up at his face.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;...fuck, how did you know where to poke?&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Warm.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The answer was a simple one, but Gregor wasn't about to question it. Instead, he tried to lean back and give the Husk easier access to his lower half, biting his own lip as he allowed the taboo nature of what he was doing to fuel his arousal. This was so fucked, but he wanted it so badly purely because it was a fucked thing to do.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;After a moment to pause and let out some kind of preparatory gurgle, the creature's tendrils began to slowly make their move, gently stroking up the base of his shaft and kneading at his balls with an unusually elegant touch. The strange, slick skin tightened as it began to gently pump up and down, and Gregor felt the muscles through his body quickly tighten as it came to terms with what was happening.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Gazing right the Husk's 'face', he looked for any kind of emotion, feeling his stomach churn as he remembered what the beast was. Its grip on his cock strengthened as it picked up the pace, another ominous groan leaving the broken suit as the parasite within started to shift. All three tendrils started to lap at his sensitive skin, the two around his cock moving against one another as they broke their rhythm, soft strokes from the pulsating feelers making him huff between clenched teeth.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The third tongue was the mystery, though. Gregor had never really paid much attention to his balls, but he was getting an unusual amount of pleasure from feeling them cupped and lightly squeezed from so many directions at once. He had no idea how long a Husk's parasitic tentacles could become, but there was something about the way that it handled down to his lower half which suggested that he was only seeing the bare minimum.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;It had only been about ten seconds, but he was already forced to straighten his spine as he felt the pressure building again, his hips muscles tugging on the base of his own shaft as the Husk continued its bizarre attempt at pleasuring him. It was usually sensual and soft, and he had to avert his eyes from the monster's broken faceplace to convince himself that this situation was in any way normal.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Relax. Please.&quot; Moving like a puppet with far too many strings, the infested suit raised one hand through the dense water of the wreck's interior and brushed it against Gregor's cheek, rubbing its thumb across his chin as its body let out horrific creaking noises. &quot;Enjoy.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Another heavy shiver ran through the man's spine as he felt the tongues tangled around his cock moving a little faster, trying to draw something out of him. The Husk knew his body better than he had expected, probably because it had eaten the corpse of whoever it used to be: the parasite understood every muscle, every weak spot, and every little movement he could make. Another squeeze to the underside of his sack made him choke on the water in his throat as it sent a burst of warmth across his hips, his pulse suddenly speeding up before he could react.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Unsure how to handle the mixture of shame and unrelenting neediness that was starting to pool in his mind, Gregor covered his eyes with the back of his arm, groaning at nothing in particular. &quot;Fuck, don't... this is so fucking wrong...&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The Husk's movements relaxed for a moment, and it felt like it was about to pull away, but the parasite currently dwelling inside Gregor spoke up in the lull of activity, projecting itself into his thoughts like a heavy weight. &quot;Good. Incubator. Deserve. Treat.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;I'm not some animal! I'm...&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;His entire body flared up as he tried to scramble for the end of that sentence, his cock still twitching as the two tongues idly stroked and rubbed at the weaker points along his shaft.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;...for fuck's sake, fine, I'm going to hell for this either way.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;A rumble of satisfaction left the Husk as it resumed its movements, lowering its head down close to his waistline as it seemed to observe his little pelvic jerks and bucks with each change of pace or angle it applied. He was half expecting it to suddenly infect him in this moment of weakness, but instead, it was only teasing him more and more, coaxing another round of tension out of his muscles whenever he managed to adapt. Even without a need for oxygen, he was still gasping rapidly in time with his thumping pulse, his mouth letting out an increasingly loud series of gruff but desperate pants and pleas.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The way that the strange alien tongue-skin brushed against his twitching member only made it harder and harder for him to resist how alluring it felt, especially since it was goading his balls to empty themselves with each little poke and stroke in the valley between each of his nuts. With a gentle squirm, it slipped further around Gregor's rear, gliding past his legs and delivering a few careful caresses to the area near his ass. As much as he wasn't used to that kind of thing, there was something about the Husk's movement that made him almost consider it.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;No, don't, not in... not in there.&quot; He was panicking, but not because he was terrified of the creature. It more that he didn't know what it was capable of, what it would do to this body. &quot;...don't stick that fucking thing inside me...&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Gregor's brain reminded him that there'd be time to experiment with some kinkier stuff later, something that he immediately realised was extremely goddamn weird even in a situation like this. He didn't know why he wanted the Volonaceps Calyx to have another chance at testing out his insides in the future, but as much as he tried to deny it, his brain was definitely brewing up the idea of the infested suit ramming him against a wall and burying some fleshy protrusion in his guts.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;The Husk paused for a moment, burbling to itself, then seemingly accepted his demands. It withdrew the tentacle that was hovering only a few inches from his rear and began to work much harder on his cock, twisting and flexing the muscles in the other two tendrils as the third decided to join in as well. It was like having three separate hands all jacking him off at once, urging him to break in some weird display of either affection or control.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Do. Not. Fight.&quot; The voice inside him synchronised with the speech of the Husk currently wearing him down, both bouncing around inside his skull. &quot;Enjoy. Treat.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Scrunching up his face as the Husk decided to apply some more force and pressure, Gregor wondered if it was telling him to enjoy its treat, or if he was the treat that it wanted to enjoy. Either way, he couldn't avoid the tension that it was creating in his lower half, and he instinctively started to writhe against the wall, halfway to an orgasm but unable to get further along.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;It didn't take long for the Husk to realise this, either. The parasite continued its touches and pulls with the three tendrils, but the moment that Gregor felt it start to slow down, he got to watch it practically slam its head down on his cock. Almost immediately, he could feel the bizarre, fleshy insides of what used to be a human's suit pressing against the head, the entire mass moving and pulsating like it was some kind of living fleshlight. It was bizarre, like having his cock shoved into multiple competing mouths at once, and he felt his limbs all tense up at once.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Holy shit, what are-&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Silent.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Gregor instantly clammed up, feeling the parasite within him slowly spreading back to his vocal chords. Terror shot through him as he wondered if this was about to be his real infection, and that his use as a mostly-unaltered human was coming to an end. The back of his throat grew heavy and his insides started to shift uneasily as he felt the soft flesh swallowing up his cock like a deep, silky void. &#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Every squirming or pressing movement that he felt against his lower body took more and more focus away from the rest of his situation, even as he felt his throat getting tight. He wasn't sure what to feel or what to think, but the constant massaging across the entirety of his cock's length was draining his energy. He just wanted it to end, he was desperate to get that release that he had been begging for in his mind for a full week, if not more.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;He came before he was ready, his balls suddenly tightening and demanding that he clench his hands against the metal flooring to steady himself. Whatever dignity he had managed to keep while letting a literal parasite suck him off was completely gone at this point, and he moaned out loud at the way that his hips stiffened, bucking slightly with each little jet of semen that burst from his body. The insides of the Husk refused to budge at all, squeezing down against him like it was trying to milk every last drop that he had in reserve.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;It was only when the beast pulled away that Gregor realized he was already empty, or at least spent to the point that nothing else would get him back to that state for a good while. Panting into the open waters and allowing his limbs to slowly relax until they turned numb and clumsy, he felt the parasite in his throat retreat again, and realised that it was meant to be some kind of edging - at least, hopefully. He didn't really have the focus to think about it.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;&quot;Good. Rest.&quot;&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;He didn't have the energy to respond, and simply nodded, catching his breath and trying to slow his pulse back to normal. His head would clear eventually, but he could just enjoy the warm, electric high for now.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;It may have been a very fucked up thing to do, but that had been the best head that Gregor had gotten since he arrived on Europa. Maybe next time he'd see how far he could take things." pickingtime="0" canbepicked="False" allowingameediting="False" msg="Deep Within The Throat" />
  </Item>
</ItemAssembly>