<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ItemAssembly name="Logbook Vaporeon is quite hot" description="" hideinmenus="false">
  <Item name="" identifier="handheldterminal" ID="2017" rect="-9,-2,17,23" noninteractable="False" nonplayerteaminteractable="False" allowswapping="True" rotation="0" scale="0.25" spritecolor="255,255,255,255" inventoryiconcolor="255,255,255,255" containercolor="255,255,255,255" condition="100" invulnerabletodamage="False" tags="smallitem,logic" displaysidebysidewhenlinked="False" disallowedupgrades="" spritedepth="0.55" hiddeningame="False">
    <Holdable holdpos="0,0" holdangle="30" swingamount="0,0" swingspeed="0" swingwhenholding="False" swingwhenaiming="False" swingwhenusing="False" pickingtime="0" canbepicked="True" allowingameediting="True" msg="ItemMsgPickUpSelect" />
    <Terminal welcomemessage="\n\n\n\n\n\n\n\nIt's Christmas Day, and your extended family has shown up to your house. Your cousins, uncles, and even people you forgot you're supposed to know and have to make awkward small talk to. This'd be a great day if it wasn't for your life partner, Vaporeon, tormenting you every step of the way. Even when you woke up, there she was next to you, one paw one your shoulder and another as close as she could get to that place. You would've done her right then and there if it wasn't for the fact you were super self conscious about anyone being able to tell you had just done something sexual. When you went go greet people, she stretched out a lot more than she usually does. She knew what she was doing, she was just upset that it wasn't you, and you were too. During dinner, once you had emptied your plate, a relative asked you that dammed question. &quot;So, do you have a girlfriend?&quot; This caused Vaporeon to jump onto your lap, and lay on her back, excited eyes piercing your calm facade. You could've lost it then and there in front of every family member you have, but you managed to play it off and say &quot;No.&quot; This carried some truth, however, since Vaporeon isn't your girlfriend. She's your wife. Then, once everyone went out to play some sport (you obviously weren't paying attention) you went to the kitchen to throw the plates that weren't picked up in the sink or the trash, and there she was. Vaporeon had literally set herself out on a silver platter, and was doing the downward facing dog, ass to you. She looked over her small and barely noticeable shoulders at you, and you could faintly see heart shapes in her pupils. You pick up one of the plates as you throw it's contents on yourself. It isn't that comfortable to have gravy and beans on your rather thin t-shirt but it won't matter for that long anyways. You go seek out one of your fellow adults there and explain to them that you &quot;accidentally spilled some food on yourself and need to go take a bath&quot;. They go tell the others, and you're now free for a while. You go to your room, pick up your phone and a new outfit, and then head to the bathroom. Thankfully, Vaporeon had been following you through all of this, so you can easily pick her up and bring her. Once you get in the bathroom, you lock the door, run the water, and then undress. Vaporeon practically tries to tear your boxers off once your pants hit the floor, and right as her mouth is about envelop your rock hard dick, you pick her up. You had almost forgotten the most important thing, the music. You unlock your phone as Vaporeon uses a soft water gun on your dick, nearly causing you to just fuck her right then and there. You put on some song and bring her into the tub. As you sit down and lean forward to turn the water off, she jumps out of your arms and seemingly almost bites your dick off. Instead, you're greeted with the pleasurable sensation of her warm mouth instead of the pain of teeth, and this just pulls you into the frenzy she's in. You move to to sitting position and raise her ass to your face. There's probably more liquid right in front of you than there is in the bath. You dig right into the delicious display in front of you, and you savor the sweet taste of your wife while she moans through the meat in her mouth. Your tongue explores every fold it can find and rubs against every wall it can find. Vaporeon can't focus on sucking while you're doing that, so her mouth moves with the rest of her. You feel a geyser of liquid as Vaporeon reaches orgasm, and you swish it around in your mouth and swallow it like the ambrosia it is to her. Your arms reach to turn Vaporeon backwards so the main event can start, but she does it herself. She raises her butt over your dick and looks you right in the eyes, which reminds you of something. She knows what this holiday is, she got you a present last year. That means that this could only be her present to you, undying and unconditional love shown in the best way she knows how as she starts to lower herself onto you. She would've finished if you hadn't grabbed her, moved into missionary position, and slammed right into her. She let out a surprised yelp as you reached right into her womb, spreading the entrance wide open. Every thrust back into her did the same as she kept letting out a mixture between a moan and a yelp. You lowered yourself onto her, and she raised herself up so that you and her could come together in a deep passionate kiss as you came inside of her. You could tell that you came enough for it to leak out past your dick, but you didn't care as you went for another round. This continued for a while, until she was satisfied. Then you remembered the guests, hurried up to exit the bath, and found your family absent. Apparently they had all assumed you had fell asleep in the bath after the large amount of Turkey you ate. They had left the presents they brought for you and took the ones you left under the tree for them. You found a decent watch, a SD card, and a ton of clothes while unboxing your presents with Vaporeon. Of course, you could smell arousal whenever you took off various articles of clothing to try the new ones on. Then, there was only one present under the tree left. You knew exactly what was in it, and unboxed it. A bottle with a childproof lock lay within the cardboard, and you quickly showed the label to Vaporeon. A wide smile grew on her face as you opened it and took a pill from inside. It was your present to Vaporeon, name brand energy supplements, and she'd soon find out why you were the one taking it. That night, you and her went to sleep minutes before midnight, with each other in loving embraces, smiles on both faces, and Vaporeon dyed white." pickingtime="0" canbepicked="False" allowingameediting="False" msg="Vaporeon is quite hot" />
  </Item>
</ItemAssembly>